what's up everyone tv5 here with a very  special review today now you may have  been wondering why the [ __ ] i've what  i've been sad for the past week and you  guessed it [ __ ] i was banned again  last week i was giving a [ __ ] strike  for like one of my videos which  unfortunately you may have noticed is  gone like this the song the hedgehog and  the grassy ball video  ever that [ __ ] was deleted by having a  school shooting or some [ __ ] and they  told me it was being insensitive  like i don't know i don't give a [ __ ]  although  i i tried appealing but youtube was like  uh uh  back the [ __ ] up like your band  and this video is being taken down like  are you kidding me but it's like i i i  can't do anything like  all i could do is just sit and wear some  [ __ ] until like my strike went away  there was a great episode  that i'm sure we all know  i'm stuck i don't even call like out of  destruction  and the point of the episode is that  like saga so you know like  swap out factories and [ __ ]  and and max says like  it sucks because the factories are just  constantly being rebuilt like  really fast because like robots like  building them too fast for somebody  sonya and the rest of the freedom  fighter mobius to like destroy them and  [ __ ]  and  and anyways like me being bad is a lot  like that [ __ ] like you can ban me for  like a week but i'll just keep coming  back like those factories  anyways the thing about the sleepover  video is that don't worry [ __ ] like  it'll be re-uploaded i'll have to cut  out the offensive [ __ ]  anyways you make a lot of [ __ ]  stories short [ __ ] like out i'm  undead  sup everyone back again  like i i forgot to film this power  during the rest of the video right now  i'm like sitting on the toilet taking a  huge [ __ ] dumping [ __ ]  and i i forgot to say this  the sleepover video that was like bad  and [ __ ] for like going against the  terms and services of youtube  that [ __ ] ain't gotta be gone forever  [ __ ] you picking up on pointing down  that's right  i'm like i i feel i needed to say this  because like i need my fans to know like  this is for you [ __ ] like i care  about you you need to know  where the [ __ ] this video is going  i don't care about you enough to like  get all the trouble they go [ __ ] [ __ ]  so bear with me  anyways if  i'll be uploading the video again but  two or three minutes will be cut  anyways yeah like  the old video will always be here in our  house and some [ __ ]  and yeah